Guide to the Miscellaneous human sexuality periodicals,circa 1950-2003
Miscellaneous human sexuality periodicals,circa 1950-2003
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Miscellaneous human sexuality periodicals, circa 1950-2003
7687
9 cubic feet
Printed materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Mostly small runs of periodicals on a variety of human sexuality subjects, including lesbians, gay men, bisexuals, transsexuals and transgender people, AIDS, feminism, and gender and sexual identity. Titles may be published in the United States or internationally.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Mostly small runs of periodicals on a variety of human sexuality subjects, including lesbians, gay men, bisexuals, transsexuals and transgender people, AIDS, feminism, and gender and sexual identity. Titles may be published in the United States or internationally. Includes conference brochures from the 1963 and 1964 conferences of ECHO, East Coast Homophile Organizations. Bringing together the Daughters of Bilitis, the Janus Society, and the New York City and Washington, DC chapters of the Mattachine Society, ECHO was the first attempt to create a national coalition of organizations focused on equal rights for lesbians and gay men.
SUBJECTS
Names:
East Coast Homophile Organizations (U.S.).
Subjects:
AIDS (Disease)--Periodicals; Lesbians--Periodicals; Gay men--Periodicals; Sex in mass media.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Read the following for information regarding finding periodicals:
All the individual titles that comprise this collection are included in the bibliographies of U.S. and international periodicals in the Human Sexuality Collection, available at http://rmc.library.cornell.edu/HSC/per.htm. If no call number is listed next to a title on that page or the collection number 7687 is listed then the item should be found in this miscellaneous collection and can be requested by the box number using the listing below.
RELATED MATERIALS
Male Model Pornography Magazines Single Issues, #7633
Heterosexual and Miscellaneous Pornography Periodicals, #7739
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- .10: A Newsletter for & About Lesbian Gay Bisexual Transgendered Questioning Youth for Youth by Youth (Box 1)
  Subject: LGBT youth
  Publisher: PRYSM
  Publication Country: United States
  Publication City: (Cleveland, OH)
- +VE (Box 1)
  Subject: Health, HIV/AIDS
  Publication Country: England
  Publication City: Middlesex
- 10%: Maine's monthly newspaper for lesbians and gay men (Box 1)
  Subject: Alternative local newspaper
- 1993 Lesbian and Gay National March on Washington Update Newsletter (Box 1)
  Subject: Politics
  Publication City: Washington, D.C.
- 24 Hour Gay Action Guide (Box 1)
  Subject: Directory
  Publication City: (New York, NY)
- 810: Newsletter of the Gay People's Union (NYU) (Box 1)
  Subject: Education
  Publisher: NYU
- A Different Light (Box 1)
  Publisher: (A Different Light Bookstore)
- AAC Lifelines (newsletter of the AIDS Action Committee) (Box 1)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Health
  Publication City: Boston, MA
- AAHA (American Association of Homes for the Aging) Provider News AIDS Overview (Box 1)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS
- AASECT Book of Abstracts (Box 1)
  Subject: Health, Education, Therapy
  Publication City: New York, NY
- Abe Lincoln's Digest: Monthly Newsletter for Republican Lesbians and Gay Men (Box 1)
  Publication City: Los Angeles, CA
- Access Line (Box 1)
  Subject: Community
  Publication City: (Waterloo, IA)
- Ace News (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Savannah, GA)
- ACLU of Oregon Newsletter (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Portland, OR)
- ACQC News (AIDS Center of Queens County) (Box 1)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Community
  Publication City: Richmond Hill, NY
- ACT Volunteer Bulletin (Box 1)
  Publication Country: Canada
  Publication City: Toronto, Ontario
- Adam International (Box 1)
  Publication Country: (Germany)
  Publication City: (Munchen)
- Affirmation: United Methodists for Gay and Lesbian Concerns (Box 1)
  Subject: Religious
  Publication City: (Evanston, IL)
- Affirmative Actoin Coordinating Center (AACC) News (Box 1)
  Publication City: (New York)
- AGLA News (Alliance for Gay & Lesbian Artists in the Entertainment Industry) (Box 1)
- AIDS Action Committee News (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Boston, MA)
- AIDS Action Project Newsletter (Box 1)
  Publication City: Chicago, IL
- AIDS Alert (Box 1)
  Publication City: Atlanta, GA
- AIDS Committee Update (Box 1)
  Publisher: (Delaware Lesbian & Gay Health Advocates)
- AIDSINFO Digest (Box 1)
- AIDS News (Box 1)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Comics
- AIDS Newsletter (Florida Keys Memorial Hospital) (Box 1)
- AIDS Patient Care (Box 1)
- AIDS Policy Reports (Box 1)
  Publisher: (Seattle-King County Department of Public Health)
- AIDS Treatment Data Network (Box 1)
- AIDS Update (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Memphis, TN)
- AIDSCom: Reducing HIV Transmission through Education and Communication (Box 1)
- AIX (AIDS Information Exchange) (Box 1)
- Alert: News from the UFMCC on AIDS Legislation, Educaiton, Research and Treatment (Box 1)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Religious
  Publisher: (The Universal Fellowship of Metropolitan Community Churches)
  Publication City: (Los Angeles)
- ALGCC 1998 Membership Directory & Buyers Guide (Albuquerque Lesbian and Gay Chamber of Commerce) (Box 1)
  Subject: Business
  Publication City: (Albuquerque, NM)
- ALGPC Newsletter: Austin Lesbian/Gay Political Caucus (Box 1)
  Publication City: Austin, TX
- Alive (Box 1)
  Publication City: (New England)
- Aliveness Newsletter (Box 1)
  Publisher: The Aliveness Project
  Publication Country: United states
  Publication City: (Minneapolis, MN)
- All Together (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Chicago)
- Alliance from gays and lesbians of Oswego State (Box 1)
- Alliance News (Box 1)
  Subject: Lesbian, Gay, News
  Publication City: (Tarrant County, TX)
- Alternative (Box 1)
  Subject: News
  Publication City: (Auburn, AL)
- Alternative (Box 1)
  Subject: African-American
- Alternative Central (Box 1)
  Publication City: Harrisburg, PA
- Alternative Communications (bulletin of the caucus of Gay and Lesbian Concerns of the Speech Communication Association) (Box 1)
- Alternative Expressions (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Buffalo, NY)
- Alternatives (Gay and Lesbian Business and Professionals Guild) (Box 1)
- Alternatives: Personal Introduction Service for the GLB Communities (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Albany, NY)
- American Gay Film Tour (Box 1)
  Subject: Entertainment
- American Grizzly (Box 1)
  Subject: Gay male, Bears
  Publication City: Louisvillle, KY
- AMSA News: Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual People in Medicine (Box 1)
  Subject: Medicine
  Publication City: (Reston, VA)
- Angel Talk (Box 1)
  Subject: Arts, Gay arts, Gay male
  Publication City: Oradell, NJ
- Announcer, The: Newsletter of the Hampton Roads Gay and Lesbian Alliance (Box 1)
- Anonymous: A Journal for the Woman Writer (Box 1)
  Subject: Literary
  Publication City: (Fresno, CA)
- Another World Magazine (Box 1)
  Subject: Gay male, Entertainment, News
  Publication City: Little Rock, AR
- Anthropological Research Group on Homosexuality (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Pacific Palisades, CA)
- APHRE Newsletter (Alliance to Protect Human Rights & Equality) (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Athens, Ohio)
- Applesource (Box 1)
  Publisher: (Metropolitan Community AThletic Association of New York)
- ARC Circular (Addiction Recovery Corporation) (Box 1)
  Subject: Health
  Publication City: Waltham, MA
- Arcadia (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Ithaca, NY)
- Archives of the American Academy of Homosexual Research (Box 1)
- Ariel: The Rogue Valley Lesbian/Gay/Bi/Human Rights Newsletter (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Ashland, OR)
- Arizona Lesbian & Gay Task Force Newsletter (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Tempe, AZ)
- Arlington Gay and Lesbian Alliance News (AGLA, AGA) (Box 1)
  Publication City: Arlington, VA
- Arlington Virginia Gay Alliance News (Box 1)
  Subject: Gay, Community
- Arno Press Catalog 1975: Homosexuality (Box 1)
  Subject: Catalog
- Around The Clock (Box 1)
  Subject: News, Entertainment
  Publication City: (New Orleans)
- Artbeat (Box 1)
  Subject: Community service
  Publication City: Greensboro, NC
- Ashtray (Box 1)
  Subject: Zine
- Asian Pacific Lesbians and Gays (Box 1)
  Subject: Asian American, Pacific Islander
  Publication City: West Hollywood, CA
- Aspen Gay Ski Week (Box 1)
  Subject: Sports
  Publication City: Aspen, CO
- Association of Lesbian and Gay Social Workers (Box 1)
- Atlanta Business & Professional Guild Directory 1987-88 (Box 1)
- Atlanta Gay Central (Box 1)
- Atlantic Stampede (Box 1)
  Publisher: (Atlantic States Gay Rodeo Association)
- Aura (Box 1)
- Australian Women's Forum (Box 1)
  Subject: Women
  Publication Country: Australia
- Autumn's Season Network (Box 1)
  Subject: s/m
- Avatar (Box 1)
  Publication City: (San Jose, CA)
- Aware (Box 1)
  Subject: Gay male, Entertainment
  Publication City: (Miami, FL)
- B.C. Lambda (Broome County) (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Binghamton, NY)
- b-2k: Gay Men's Health Crisis Periodical (Box 1)
  Publisher: (GMHC)
- Baby Dyke, The Adventures of (Box 1)
  Subject: Comics, Zine
  Publication City: (Baltimore, MD)
- BAPA (Business and Professional Association) Newsletter (Box 1)
  Publication City: (West Hollywood, CA)
- Bar Association for Human Rights Report (BAHR) (Box 1)
- Bar Guide: 1973 USA International (Box 1)
- Barfly (Box 1)
- Barnard Bulletin (Box 1)
- Battering Ram, The (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Rochester, NY)
- Bay Area Gay Liberation Newsletter (Box 1)
  Publication City: (San Francisco, CA)
- Bay Area Women's News (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Oakland, CA)
- Bears Prowl (Box 1)
  Subject: Bears, Gay male, Large gay men
  Publication City: San Francisco, CA
- Because We Care (INTEGRITY/Houston) (Box 1)
  Subject: Queer, Gay, Lesbian, Religious: Episcopal
  Publication City: Houston, TX
- Bi Tribune (Box 1)
  Subject: Bisexual
  Publication City: Indianapolis, IN
- Bi-Girls: Michelle's Women's Adult Wrestling Club (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Los Angeles, CA)
- Bill Landis' Sleazoid Express (Box 1)
- Bimbox (Box 1)
- Black Forum (Box 1)
  Subject: Black
- Blackberry (Box 1)
- Blade (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Orange County and Long Beach)
- Blood brothers (Box 1)
  Subject: Gay male, Literary
- Bloomington Beacon (Box 1)
  Publication City: Bloomington, IN
- BOA (Bar Owners Association) Newsletter (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Ft. Lauderdale, FL)
- Bolt (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Harwin, CT)
- Bona (Box 1)
  Subject: Erotica, News
  Publication City: (London)
- Books Bohemian (Box 1)
  Subject: Books, Catalog
  Publication City: (Glendale, CA)
- Both Sides Now (newsletter for Maui's Gay/Bi/Lesbian Community Organization) (Box 1)
  Publication City: Maui, HI
- Box (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Koln)
- Brains: The Journal of Egghead Sexuality (Box 1)
- Branches (Box 1)
  Publisher: Duke-UNC Women's Studies Research Center
  Publication City: (Durham, NC)
- Bread Box (Box 1)
- Bridge, The (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Salt Lake City, UT)
- Bridge, The: Connecting Perspectives To Create Community (Box 1)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian
  Publication City: Knoxville, TN
- Bridge, The: Dignity/Brooklyn (Box 1)
- Broadsheet (Box 1)
  Subject: Feminist
  Publication Country: (New Zealand)
- Bronx HIV Funding Bulletin (Box 1)
- Brother: The Newsletter of the National Organization of Changing Men (Box 1)
  Subject: Men
- Bulletin (Northern California Gay Rights Chapter of ACLU) (Box 1)
- Bulletin, The (Box 1)
  Publication City: (Long Beach, CA)
- Café Magazine (Box 2)
  Subject: Entertainment, Gay arts
  Publication City: Philadelphia, PA
- Calyx (Box 2)
  Subject: Literary, Women
  Publication City: (Corvallis, OR)
- Camp NSW Newsletter (Oversize) (Box 2)
  Publication City: Sydney
- Can We Talk? (San Francisco AIDS Foundation) (Box 2)
- Capital "Q" News (Box 2)
  Subject: Gay, News
  Publication City: Tenino, WA
- Care Notes (Box 2)
  Publisher: (Nashville Council on AIDS Resources)
  Publication City: (Nasshville, TN)
- Carl Driver's Gay Europe (Box 2)
  Subject: Directory, Travel
  Publication City: (Springville, CA)
- Carolina Pulse (Box 2)
  Publication City: Raleigh, NC
- Carolinas Pride Guide (Box 2)
  Subject: Business, Lesbian, Gay
- Centaur Magazine (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Yucca Valley, CA)
- Center Attraction (Box 2)
  Publisher: The Lesbian/Gay Community Service Center
- Center Fold (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Central Florida)
- Center Letter (Newsletter of the Gay/Lesbian Community Center of Greater Cincinnati) (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Cincinatti, OH)
- Center Report: Annual Report of the Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Community Center (Box 2)
- CGLBMAPA (Caucus of Gay, Lesbian and Bisexual Members of the American Psychiatric Association) (Box 2)
- Chambre de Commerce Gaie du Québec: Bottin des Membres (Box 2)
  Publication Country: Montréal, Québec, Canada
- Changes in Gay Student Rights (Box 2)
  Publisher: National Gay Student Center
- Changing Woman (Box 2)
- Cherry Collection (Box 2)
  Author: Larry Weiz Subject: Comics, Erotica
  Publisher: Last Gasp
  Publication City: San Francisco
- Chicago Area Gay and Lesbian Chamber of Commerce Membership Directory (Box 2)
- Chicago Gay Alliance Newsletter (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Chicago, IL)
- Chicago Gay Pride (Box 2)
- Chicago Living in Leather (Box 2)
  Publisher: (National Leather Association)
- Chicago Pride Magazine (Box 2)
  Subject: Gay, Entertainment
- Chicago's Gay Directory 1973 (Box 2)
  Subject: directory
  Publication City: Chicago, Il
- Chippendales Calendar (1987) (Box 2)
  Subject: Heterosexual, Physique, Men
- Chips (Box 2)
  Subject: Heterosexual, Men
  Publication City: Crestwood, NY
- Choruspondence (Box 2)
  Publisher: (Gay Men's Choir of Los Angeles)
- Chosen Books (Box 2)
  Subject: Books
  Publication City: Detroit, MI
- Chrome Roses Review (Box 2)
  Subject: Women motorcyclists
  Publication City: (Leroy, NY)
- Church of the Beloved Disciple Newsletter (Box 2)
- Chutzpah (Box 2)
- Ciao! (Box 2)
  Subject: Comics
  Publication City: (Sunnyvale, CA)
- Ciao! (A Newsletter Dedicated to Examining the Comic Industry's Awareness of Issues) (Box 2)
  Subject: newsletter, comics
- CItizen Action Guide (Box 2)
  Subject: Politics, Bisexual, Lesbian, Gay
  Publication City: Covington, KY
- City Health Information (Box 2)
  Subject: Gay health
- Civil Liberties Alert (Box 2)
  Publisher: ACLU
- Classy: DQ for Today's Transvestite (Box 2)
  Subject: Transvestite
- Cleis Press Catalog (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Pittsburgh)
- Cleveland NOW! (Box 2)
  Subject: Entertainment, Directory
- CLGR (Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Rights) Bulletin (Box 2)
- Clinical Courier (Box 2)
  Publisher: (National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases)
- CLOUT reach (Box 2)
  Subject: religious
- Clubs Monthly (Box 2)
  Subject: Gay male
  Publication City: Miami, FL
- Coalition News: New Coalition for Human Rights on Long Island (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Long Island, NY)
- Collective Consciousness (Box 2)
- Colorado AIDS Project Newsletter (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Denver, CO)
- Colorado Community Directory (Box 2)
- Columbia Fun Maps (Montreal and Quebec) (Box 2)
  Subject: Travel, Gay, Lesbian
- Columbia Daily Spectator (Columbia University) (Box 2)
- Columbus Free Press (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Columbus, OH)
- Come to Long Island! (Box 2)
- Communique (Northern Lambda Nord) (Box 2)
  Publication City: Caribou, ME
- Community Action News (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Brooklyn, NY)
- Community Alliance FYI (Box 2)
  Publisher: Community Alliance
  Publication City: (Sioux City, IA)
- Community Center News (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Dallas, TX)
- Community Communications (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Akron, OH)
- Community Press (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Norfolk, VA)
- Complot (Box 2)
  Publication Country: (Mexico)
- Conscience: A Newsjournal of Prochoice Catholic Opinion (Box 2)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Religious: Catholic
- Cornerstone (Box 2)
- Corsair (Santa Monica College) (Box 2)
  Subject: transgender, transsexual, transvestite, homecoming
- Counterpoints (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Boston)
- Creative Loafing (Box 2)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Alternative local newspaper
  Publication City: (Atlanta, GA)
- Critical Path AIDS Project (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Philadelphia)
- Crossbeams (GLAD Alliance newsletter) (Box 2)
- CSC Newsletter (Childhood Sexuality Circle) (Box 2)
  Subject: sexual liberation
  Publication City: (El Cajon, CA)
- Cup 1999, The (Box 2)
- CWAO News (Coalition of Women's Arts Organizations) (Box 2)
- Cybersocket Web Magazine (Box 2)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Entertainment
- Danny, The (Box 2)
- Dartmouth Lambda (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Philadelphia, PA)
- Dateline: The Magazine of Gay America (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Hollywood, CA)
- Dean Magazine (Box 2)
- Decision (Box 2)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Religious: Christian
  Publisher: Billy Graham Evangelistic Association
  Publication City: Minneapolis, MN
- Deltaphile, The (Box 2)
  Publisher: (University of Minnesota Delta Lambda Phi)
- Desert Reflections (Box 2)
- Detroit Women's Voice (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Detroit, MI)
- Dialogue (Box 2)
  Publisher: Cobb Citizens Coalition, Inc.
  Publication City: Marietta, Georgia
- Diary (Box 2)
  Subject: Women, Literary
- DIFFA On Line (Box 2)
  Publisher: (Design Industries Foundation for AIDS)
- Dignity/ NY Calendar (Box 2)
  Subject: Religious: Catholic
- Dignity: Newsletter of the Gay Catholic Community (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Washington DC)
- Dilettante (Box 2)
  Subject: Arts, Entertainment
- Diplomat Magazine (Box 2)
  Subject: People of Color
- Diversity and Division (Box 2)
- Diversity: The Lesbian Rag (Box 2)
  Publication Country: (Canada)
- Docket Update (Box 2)
  Subject: Legal
- Dorian Book Service (Box 2)
- Dorn Rosa (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Hamburg)
- Drummer: Follow Us to Where the Action is! (Box 2)
  Publisher: Dummer Publications
- East Coast Homophile Organization (Box 2)
- Eastern Hi-Lites (Box 2)
  Publisher: (Eastern Area Pioneer Women)
- EBL/ GDC: Newsletter of the East Bay Lesbian/ Gay Democratic Club (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Berkeley, CA)
- Echo Magazine (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Phoenix, AZ)
- Eclipse: Louisiana Gay Nite Life & Adult Entertainment (Box 2)
- Edcentric: A Journal of Educational Change (Box 2)
- EDGE Newsletter (Education in a Disabled Gay Environment) (Oversize) (Box 2)
  Subject: Disability Issues
- Editions Aubrey Walter (Box 2)
  Subject: Arts, Gay arts
  Publication City: (London, England)
- Education Exploration Center (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Minneapolis, Minnesota)
- EEGO In Brief (East End Gay Organization for Human Rights) (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Southampton, NY)
- Eleanor Roosevelt Gay Democratic Club (Box 2)
  Publication City: Cleveland, OH
- Electorate, The (Box 2)
  Publisher: Louisiana Electorate of Gays And Lesbians, Inc.
  Publication City: (New Orleans, LA)
- Elite (Box 2)
  Subject: Transgender
- Emerald Wave (Box 2)
  Publication City: (West Palm Beach, FL)
- Empowerment Times (Box 2)
  Subject: Youth
  Publisher: (LA Gay & Lesbian Community Services Center)
- EMV Newsletter (Ending Men's Violence) (Box 2)
  Subject: Men, Women and violent crimes
  Publication City: (Dorchester, MA)
- Enterprising Women (Box 2)
- Eon (Box 2)
  Subject: Transsexual, Transgender, Transvestite
- Equity Institute News (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Amherst, MA)
- Eric's Word (Oversize) (Box 2)
  Publisher: E.C.R. Enterprises Inc.
- Eugene Citizens for Human Rights (ECHR) (Box 2)
  Publication City: (Eugene, OR)
- Eurogames (Box 2)
  Publication Country: Germany
  Publication City: Munich
- EVLGN (East Village Lesbian & Gay Newsletter) (Box 2)
- Executive Woman (Box 2)
  Publisher: Businesswomen's Publishing Company
- Expose Magazine (Box 2)
- Faces of South Dakota (Box 3)
  Publisher: Faces of South Dakota, Inc. and Library
  Publication City: Rapid City, SD
- Facts about AIDS (Box 3)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Education
  Publisher: U.S. Department of Health and Human Services
- Fairfax Lesbian and Gay Citizens Association (FLGCA Newsletter) (Box 3)
  Publication City: Springfield, VA
- Fairfield Advocate (Box 3)
  Publisher: New Mass Media, Inc.
  Publication City: Amherst, MA
- Family Diversity (Box 3)
  Subject: Families
  Publisher: Family Diversity Project
- Family Ministries & Human Sexuality (Box 3)
  Publisher: National Council of Churches
- Family Talk (Box 3)
  Subject: Community service, Lesbian, Gay, Families
- FARO Update (Federation of AIDS-Related Organizations) (Box 3)
  Publisher: Federation of AIDS-Related Organizations
- Fashion Cares (Box 3)
  Publisher: Digital Propaganda, Inc.
- Fat Apple Review (Box 3)
  Subject: Entertainment, large gay men
  Publisher: Girth & Mirth Club of New York, Inc.
- Feedback (Box 3)
  Publisher: Southern Tier Information & Referral
  Publication City: Elmira, NY
- Fetish (Box 3)
  Subject: s/m, Sexual liberation
- Fifth Freedom Bulletin (Box 3)
  Publisher: Mattachine Society of the Niagara Frontier, Inc.
  Publication City: Buffalo, NY
- Fight the Right (Box 3)
  Publisher: Center for Constitutional Rights
- Fire! (Box 3)
  Publisher: Prometheus Foundation
- Fire This Time, The (Box 3)
  Publisher: DC Coalition of Black Gay Men and Women
- Firetruck House Flame (Box 3)
  Subject: Stanford University, College/University
  Publication City: Palo Alto, CA
- Flathead Valley Alliance (Box 3)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual
  Publisher: Flathead Valley Alliance
  Publication City: Kalispell, MT
- Florida Task Force Report, The (Box 3)
  Publisher: The Florida Taskforce, Inc.
- Focus on AIDS (Box 3)
  Publisher: AIDS Project Los Angeles
- Focus on the New Generation (Box 3)
  Subject: Youth, Religious
  Publisher: United Church Board for Homeland Minitries, Division of Christian Education
- Foot Fraternity (Box 3)
  Publisher: The Fraternity
- Forgiveness News (Box 3)
  Publisher: San Francisco Miracles Foundation
- Fortune News (Box 3)
  Subject: Prisoners
- Forum (Box 3)
  Publication City: Munchen
- Forum (National Action Forum For Older Women) (Box 3)
  Subject: Women, Aged
  Publisher: National Action Forumfor Older Women
  Publication City: Kalamazoo, MI
- Forum: A Networking Resource for Atlanta's Lesbian Community (Box 3)
  Subject: Lesbian
  Publisher: Fourth Tuesday
- Forward Observer (Box 3)
  Subject: veterans
  Publication City: (Plainville, IL)
- Forward Observer: The National Newsletter of Gay, Lesbian & Bisexual Veterans of America (Box 3)
  Subject: Veterans
  Publisher: Gay, Lesbian & Bisexual Veterans of America
  Publication City: Milwaukee, WI
- Foundation (Box 3)
  Publisher: Foundation
  Publication City: Elkhart, IN
- Fox Valley Gay Association (FVGA) (Box 3)
  Publisher: Fox Valley Gay Association
  Publication City: Streamwood, IL
- FQ: The Official Journal of the Uncircumcised Society of America (Box 3)
  Subject: Men, Health
  Publisher: Uncircumsized Society of America
- Freedom Socialist, The (Box 3)
  Subject: Feminist, Politics
  Publisher: Freedom Socialist Party
  Publication City: Seattle, WA
- Friends Newsletter (Box 3)
  Publisher: Friends In Deed
- Front Page Directory, The (Box 3)
  Subject: Directory, Lesbian, Gay, Transgender
  Publisher: The Front Page
  Publication City: Releigh, NC
- Frontlines (Box 3)
  Publisher: Outfront Minnesota
- Full Circle Calender (Box 3)
  Subject: Women, Lesbian
  Publisher: Full Circle Calendar
  Publication City: Contoocook, NH
- Further Violations of Our Rights: A Journal of Issues (Box 3)
  Author: Carol Leigh Subject: HIV/AIDS, Prostitutes
  Publisher: Carol Leigh
- FYI (Box 3)
  Subject: Labor
- G.O.A.L. Gazette (Gay Officers Action League) (Box 3)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Community, Community service
  Publisher: Gay Officers Action League Inc.